[Music]
blessings of roses Christine Oh from the
rod vanish calm registered Holistic
Nutritionist raw food lifestyle coach
and raw chef today we're making one of
my favorite curries Martha's best curry
[Music]
alright so I'm really excited to share
this recipe with you it's not
Martha's best as in Martha Stewart's is
using Martha's best papayas the best
papayas out there certified non-gmo
super ridiculously delicious strawberry
papayas honestly the best I've ever had
and you know papayas can be hard to come
by so that's why I'm reppin these
suckers you can get 10% off at Martha's
best calm if you use my coat the raw
advantage they're available year-round
will bring them right to your door so
whether you want to share them with some
friends or you know eat them in the dead
of winter or just a special treat
definitely definitely well worth that
amazing produce makes all the difference
and you're so worth it so we're using
those if you're not using Martha's best
or using just an okay kind of papaya you
may need to sub in two dates we're also
going to be using a young Thai coconut
you can find these at most Asian grocery
stores now I also really want to let you
know that this recipe is from miss
naturally Ashley in my newest book
naturally raw some dressings now these
are some of our newest favorite dressing
recipes and they're actually Woodstock
edition they're the ones we're making as
the sauce chefs in Woodstock here 2017
so if you want to get all of the
dressings click up here plus if you
haven't checked out the Woodstock fruit
festival for make sure you check it out
the Woodstock fruit festival calm and if
it's your first time going there use the
code banana and you can get 100 bucks
off so let's get right into the recipe
we'll start by opening up the Thai
coconut you can either use a coconut
jack or a sturdy chef knife like this
smashing around it then pouring out the
water about three-quarters of a cup and
use a nice spoon and start scooping all
the jelly off of the coat
gonna top as well as the inside so you
want to get any big pieces of wood off
but that little bit of brown that
attaches to the white the coconut is
totally fine looking for one cut now
something pretty cool about papayas and
coconuts and ginger too and thus this
recipe is that they're anti-parasitic
especially the seeds so it's like an
anti-parasitic curry we're gonna cut
this open reserve 1tsp of the seeds you
can optionally use if you like so in
this dressing we have one cup of
Martha's best papaya 0.75 cups of
coconut water one full cup of coconut
jelly one half a lime or one tablespoon
one green onion a medallion of fresh
ginger one to three tablespoons of your
favorite curry and the optional hot
pepper and papaya seeds
I just put your coconut water in the
blenders and martha's best papaya add in
your coconut jelly and the medallion of
ginger then you're gonna want to juice
that lime I put one teaspoon and add
that in there put in the curry powder as
much as you like and chop up the white
part of the green onion throwing that
blender as well now I like its spicy so
I'm gonna put this whole however in
there it's optional and I'm not gonna
use with a bias seeds because I'm not
really worried about parasites myself
and tastes better without but again
there's an option let's blend it in the
mighty Vitamix blender the best blender
out there get the best possible deal on
my website get free shipping shameless
blend until completely smooth add in the
green onion tops and blended a slow
speed to maintain a chunky texture
well there you have it this sauce is
done it's seriously so amazing and
creamy and sweet has really the
authentic curry flavors this is so damn
good so you can put this over anything
you want if you like this recipe like
subscribe share comment below check out
my raw recipes playlist for a whole
bunch more and again check out the
natural ear awesome dressings eBook I'm
just gonna chop up some napa cabbage one
of my favorites ever and some bell
peppers and put this over top of it for
a nice creamy curry noodle salad damn
that looks good hope you try this out
try out some martha's best papayas and
see you at Woodstock
wishing you much peace love and seasonal
fruit Mart is best the best curry sauce
around who don't forget to watch my raw
recipes playlist in the top left this
video just for you in the top right for
sure subscribe in the bottom right
figure three free ebooks in the bottom
left by signing up grab my free iPhone
app comes with 50 free recipes common
fruit vegetable carrier breakdown a food
combining chart shopping cart function
and much much more